Ghilman Faza

UI/UX Designer

% +6285155020756

www.ghilmanfaza.site

👂 Sleman, Yogyakarta

Summary

For the past two years, I've been working as a UI/UX designer while studying in the Informatics Study Program at the Indonesian Islamic University. I have a strong ability to think critically and creatively, which makes me highly qualified for the job. I'm skilled in design and programming, and I'm confident that I can compete with others in this field. My expertise lies in Design Research, UI/UX Design, as well as Mobile and Web UI Design.

Experience

DOT Indonesia - Malang, East Java, Indonesia

Feb 2023 - May 2023

UI Designer

- Created design system, wireframes, visual designs, and prototypes using Figma
- Flexible in adapting to every project required and understanding client needs for every given project
- Building relationships with colleagues by conducting meetings twice a week to enhance familiarity and chemistry needed

Alterra Academy X Kampus Merdeka - Malang, East Java, Indonesia

Feb 2022 - Aug 2022

UI/UX Designer

- Learn various UI/UX design materials from basic to advanced stages
- Produce various interfaces from mobile design to web design
- Search and find problems in Inarisk Personal app and redesign them for case studies using the design thinking method
- Become a UI/UX Designer in a team in a capstone project
- Create various needs such as userflow, wireframe, low fidelity, high fidelity to prototypes in the form of mobile app designs for users and web app designs in the form of landing pages and dashboards for admins.

UX Club Team - Islamic University Of Indonesia

Oct 2020 - Nov 2021

Challenge UX Designer

- Learn the fundamental of UI/UX design
- Share insights about user experience and user interfaces
- Complete challenges given by UX club to add to portfolio
- Pay attention to every detail with Pixel Perfect in mobile app interface design

Big Project In Informatics - Islamic University Of Indonesia

Sep 2020 - Jan 2022

Informatics Students

- Coordinate web design projects for a tutorial application
- Act as a front-end developer to implement the designs
- Assist in community decision-making through an intelligent system that uses the SAW (Simple Additive Weighting) method
- Build a web design interface with dashboard views and surveys as the main features of a big project
- Conduct research to find the latest innovations based on community needs and competitors
- Create low and high-fidelity designs to enhance the developed web designs

Education

Licenses & Certification

Certificate MSIB Kampus Merdeka - Alterra Academy

Yogyakarta, Indonesia. 2019 - Present

Organization

Coordinator Creative Information And Publication Of Laboratory Assistant

Yogyakarta, Indonesia. 2020 - 2022

Laboratorium Informatika UII

Deputy Coordinator For Supplies, Publications, Decoration And Documentation

Yogyakarta, Indonesia. 2020 - 2022

Unisi Music Community

Tools & Skills

Mobile DesignBootstrapWireframingMazeWeb DesignAndroid StudioPrototypingHTML/CSSUI/UX DesignFigmaSocial Media Content CreationProduct Design